Okay!
Which one does NOT belong?
A.
Radish,
B.
Cabinet,
C.
Chair,
or D.
Dresser?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
The answer is...
A,
radish!
Chair,
cabinet,
and dresser are all furniture.
Radish is a vegetable,
so it does not belong.
Here's one,
a picture puzzle!
Where does the dot move next?
A.
Top-right,
B.
Bottom-left,
C.
Top,
or D.
Bottom?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
The answer is...
A,
top-right!
The dot moves three spots counter-clockwise
around the grid each step,
so the next spot is top-right.
Here's one,
a number series!
Three,
six,
nine,
fifteen,
twenty-four,
and then...
what comes next?
A.
Forty-four,
B.
Thirty-seven,
C.
Thirty-nine,
or D.
Forty?
Five seconds!
TIME'S UP!
What's your answer?
Comment below and I'll let you
know if you're a Certified Smart Fella!